fxcm.com 2012-05-10

# Privacy Policy, We protect our clients' privacy. | FXCM

**FXCM respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients, current clients, and applicants.**

### Personal Information

When you apply for or maintain a live account with FXCM, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. Such information may include:

  * application information: Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name, address, birth date, Social Security number, occupation, assets, and income; 
  * transaction information: Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries, and our responses;
  * verification information: Information necessary to verify your identity, such as a passport or driver's license. Examples also include background information about you we receive from public records or from other entities not affiliated with FXCM. The USA PATRIOT Act requires us to collect information and take actions necessary to verify your identity.

### About Cookies

Cookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. FXCM may set and access FXCM cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. FXCM or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with FXCM's products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable.

### Security Technology

FXCM uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than FXCM while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our Web sites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data.

### Sharing Information with Our Affiliates

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as, but not limited to, servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, or to aid in the trading activity of the company, its affiliates, or employees, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us as well as companies that have an ownership interest in our company. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above, such as your name, address, trading and account information. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent FXCM does in accordance with this Policy.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

FXCM does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with FXCM, including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to FXCM. Non-affiliated companies that assist FXCM in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that FXCM dictates. Additionally, in order to comply with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (“CFTC”) regulations, FXCM is obligated to regularly transmit copies of all account statements of any Client who is a related person of a Retail Forex Counterparty, as defined in Section 5.18 of the to the CFTC Regulation of Off-Exchange Retail Foreign Exchange Transactions and Intermediaries, to the related Retail Forex Counterparty. A related person when used in reference to a Retail Forex Counterparty means any general partner, officer, director, owner of more than ten percent of the equity interest, associated person or employee of the Retail Forex Counterparty, and any relative or spouse of any of the foregoing persons, or any relative of such spouse, who shares the same home as any of the foregoing persons. Furthermore, we may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your express consent. We want you to know that FXCM will not sell your personal information.

### Regulatory Disclosure

Under limited circumstances, FXCM may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission. 

### Opt Out

You are not required to supply any of the personal information that we may request; however, failure to do so may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account or to provide services to you. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete, and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.

If you do not wish to have your personal information disclosed to our affiliates or other third parties as described in this Policy, please contact us via e-mail at: [compliance@fxcm.com](mailto:compliance@fxcm.com)

or send your request to: 

**Forex Capital Markets LLC**  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
55 Water St., 50th Floor  
New York, NY 10041

Please be advised, that if we receive such instruction we will not be able to service your account and must close any open and funded accounts you have.

High Risk Investment Warning: Trading foreign exchange on margin carries a high level of risk, and may not be suitable for all investors. The high degree of leverage can work against you as well as for you. Before deciding to trade foreign exchange you should carefully consider your investment objectives, level of experience, and risk appetite. The possibility exists that you could sustain a loss of some or all of your initial investment and therefore you should not invest money that you cannot afford to lose. You should be aware of all the risks associated with foreign exchange trading, and seek advice from an independent financial advisor if you have any doubts. Please click here to read full risk warning.

FXCM is a registered Futures Commission Merchant and Retail Foreign Exchange Dealer with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission and is a member of the National Futures Association. NFA # 0308179 

FXCM Inc., a publicly traded company listed on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE: FXCM), is a holding company and its sole asset is a controlling equity interest in FXCM Holdings, LLC. Forex Capital Markets, LLC ("FXCM LLC") is a direct operating subsidiary of FXCM Holdings, LLC. All references on this site to "FXCM" refer to FXCM Inc. and its consolidated subsidiaries, including FXCM Holdings, LLC and Forex Capital Markets, LLC.

Please note the information on this website is intended for retail customers only, and certain representations herein may not be applicable to Eligible Contract Participants (i.e., institutional clients) as defined in the Commodity Exchange Act §1(a)(12).

§FXCM’s liquidity providers include global banks, financial institutions, prime brokers and other market makers. 

If you ever experience performance difficulties with your trading account, [click here](http://support.fxcm.com/status/).
